[ indistinct chatter in distant hallway ]
[ door opens ]
[ running footsteps ]
[ boy ] Come on . Pass , pass . I 'm open .
[ man ] A little slower in the hallway , please .
[ boy 2 ] You 're an idiot .
[ girl ] What if no one asks me ? Like last year ?
- [ boy 3 ] I 'll get that , milady . - [ laughter ]
- [ school bell ringing ] - [ indistinct chatter ]
[ chatter continues ]
[ door opens ]
[ piano music playing ]
[ chuckles softly ]
[ girl ] You didn 't tell me you played piano .
[ Maren ] Hey .
You are here . Where have you been ?
You weren 't in Home Ec . All week .
I got to slip to work on the yearbook .
We missed our deadline with Jostens .
Oh . How 's it look ?
You 're not gonna be in it , by the way .
Mr. Esser said he reminded you three times
- to get your picture taken . - [ plays piano ]
Hey , so my dad 's doing inventory all night ,
and Kim and Jackie are sleeping over .
Come too .
[ continues playing piano ]
No , my dad won 't let me .
So sneak out . After he goes to bed .
How would I get there ?
You 're down in Southwind , right ?
You know the power lines that go up the hill ?
That 's Chesapeake Road at the top . I 'm right there .
You said you wanna make more friends here .
[ students chattering ]
Hey . Come on , you drive .
- [ boy ] Okay . - [ girl ] Take care . Bye .
[ men laughing and chattering ]
Hey . That was good on the road .
Gotta work on that parking some more ...
but good .
You think it 's gonna rain tonight ?
Don 't think it 's supposed to .
[ can pops open ]
[ grunts ] Got homework ?
Just reading , Dad .
The man has attempted suicide .
I think he realized
that this scheme that he had been involved in ,
about which he had always been extremely guilty .
I mean , he 's ... he 's , I think , the only person
in this entire scheme to have voluntarily walked out on it .
Some people were annoyed with it , upset with it ,
and ... but went along with it . Others enjoyed it
because they were making a lot of money out of it .
Dowd was the only person who had the character ...
' Night , Dad .
[ man on TV ] and the moral fiber ...
Yeah . Sleep good .
[ man on TV ] to walk out on this scheme
long before anybody knew about it ,
because it disgusted him .
I mean , the prospect of actually
walking into Donald Manes ' office
and paying him cash ...
[ wind blowing ]
- [ muffled music playing ] - [ muffled chatter ]
[ panting ]
Hang on . Okay .
- Hey . - Hey .
You got prickers all over you . Come in .
[ indistinct chatter ]
[ Kim ] So you can 't spend the night ?
[ Maren ] Not all night .
I should be back by 6 : 00 to be safe .
Jesus .
I 'll just head out when you guys wanna sleep .
So where 'd you move here from anyway ?
Eastern shore .
Is your mom in the picture ?
Sherry says you only have a dad .
[ knock on table ]
" Cinnamon Glaze . "
We 're trying to talk .
[ Sherry ] Kim , give me your hand .
[ Kim ] Never mind about your mom .
It 's none of my business , anyway .
[ inhales deeply ]
I don 't have any memories of her .
Or photos even .
My dad wouldn 't tell me anything .
Try that . It 's called " Copper Fever . "
It 's too orange .
- [ bones crunching ] - [ screaming ]
Oh , my God !
Maren , stop it !
Stop ! Stop it !
Maren , stop ! Maren , no !
- Jackie ! - [ continues screaming ]
Maren , stop !
Jackie ! Jackie , help !
Jackie , help !
[ panting ]
[ banging on door ]
You didn 't .
In the car in three minutes .
Whatever you can take in three minutes .
Go !
Shit .
Move , Maren !
When the cops get here , we have to be good and gone .
Dad ?
[ sighs ]
[ yawning ]
Dad ?
[ breathing heavily ]
[ button clicks ]
[ Maren 's father on tape ] I 've got some things to say .
And then ...
I want you to make sure this , uh ...
this tape is good and destroyed . Don 't keep it .
This has got my voice on it .
You 're not going to see me again , Maren .
I can 't ...
help you anymore .
[ Maren crying ]
I can 't do anything else , either .
Call the cops or whatever somebody might do in my place .
So I gotta leave you to figure it out for yourself .
Like your mother did .
I 'm sorry . You know what I mean now .
I don 't know how much ...
how much of what I 'm gonna say you 'll remember .
[ sighs ] Yeah . Never was sure .
But just in case ,
I 'll tell you everything I know .
First time was when you were three .
[ indistinct talking on TV ]
[ newscaster ] Downey has the crowd screaming
at Towson State University .
The topic was the most controversial issue
on this year 's Maryland ballot ,
the gun ban referendum .
The majority of those in the audience
seem to be against the ban ,
but we found those on both sides of the issue .
[ woman ] I think it 's a good law ,
if she gets guns off the streets ,
and that 's what we need most .
[ man ] I just don 't think it 's fair
for all the innocent people that wanna get a gun
to protect themselves .
Just making it easier for criminals to have them than honest people .
[ man 2 ] I don 't want them comin ' in my living room and tell me what I can and can 't buy .
Y 'all think if you take the guns away from everybody ,
you have less shooting with the whole nine-yards ,
the criminals and the innocent people .
Hi .
Uh ...
I need to get here .
What 's the closest I can get by bus ?
Well , looks like Detroit Lakes .
Three transfers .
Frederick , Maryland , Columbus and Minneapolis .
One way ? 83 .
How much to Columbus ?
Shouldn 't you be in school ?
You 'd think .
I don 't know what that means .
Means I 'm 18 , in the state of Maryland ,
and I can decide for myself where I should be .
I 'm gonna need to see a driver 's license or a learner 's permit .
You can see a birth certificate .
Come on .
Just to Columbus ?
It 's 49 .
50 .
[ passengers chattering ]
[ Maren 's father ] I had a sitter for you then .
[ chuckles ] Her name was Penny .
When I came in , she was on the bathroom floor .
There was ... so much blood .
Her face was chewed up bad ,
but the worst of it was her neck .
She must 've been holding you when you started in on her .
Her hands , all chewed up . I ...
I thought you were dead too .
That somebody had done you both ,
but you were sleepin ' .
When I turned you over , I saw the blood on your mouth .
You had something in your cheek .
I fished it out . It was soft , like a wad of gum .
It had a little hole in it .
Where an earring would go .
I remember thanking God she hadn 't been wearing any ,
you could 've choked .
I got the body out ,
I bleached the place three times ,
and then packed us up and left .
They never found where I put her .
That was the last time I used our real last name .
Now you know why .
Nothin ' happened for a few years . I relaxed .
You had to start school and I thought ...
I thought you wouldn 't do it in public ,
and you didn 't .
But you got clever .
So fucking clever .
[ sighs ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ rain pattering ]
[ thunder continues rumbling ]
I didn 't mean to scare you .
[ breathing shakily ]
You waiting for the bus ?
Well , no , missy . I ...
I came lookin ' for you .
Do I know you ?
I guess not in the way you mean .
I smelled you .
You probably smell me now .
When was the last time you fed ?
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ sniffs ]
[ Maren ] Stop , stop , stop there . Stop .
You haven 't in a long time . [ sniffs ]
I 'll say ...
many months .
At least .
You can smell that ?
[ chuckles ] Oh , sure .
You can ...
You can smell lots of things if you know how .
[ sniffs ]
And we just smell anyway . [ laughs ]
Whether we ate or not .
Hmm .
Come on , missy .
Come on .
[ Maren ] Where are we goin ' ?
Just here , someplace dry and safe .
I 'm Sullivan .
Friends call me Sully .
Maren .
Is this your house ?
Listen , Maren ,
don 't worry . I 'm okay .
I got rules .
One , number one
is never , never , ever eat an Eater .
Think you can follow that too ?
All right .
I 'll fix some dinner for us .
I smelled you from the yard , little missy . Come on .
This far ?
[ Sully ] Round the back . We 'll talk inside .
The Sully , he found these little Cornish hens
in the freezer .
These hens ,
they look like they had a good life .
Thought I was the only one .
Are there lots of us ?
Not lots .
But more ...
more than you 'd think .
You 've met a few , sure , that you know of .
[ bones snapping ]
You never had anyone take a interest in you ?
[ stutters ] A double take ?
[ chuckles ]
Just always thought ...
You just thought some people are creepy .
It 's better if we all steer clear of one another .
We 're dangerous to non-Eaters ,
but we can hurt one another just as bad .
I hope you 're hearing me on this .
[ thunder rumbling ]
You sound like my dad .
Your daddy find out about you ?
What about you ?
You basically just said steer clear of people like us .
But you came looking for me .
[ chuckling ]
Smart .
When I saw you 're just a girl on your own ,
I thought ...
you might be hungry .
For hens ?
[ breathing heavily ]
No .
Who lives here ?
Well , go and look .
[ Maren sniffing ]
Use your nose .
What do you smell ?
Is there someone dead up there ?
Describe it .
Metallic .
Like blood ?
No , like mud .
Something tangy .
But not like rotten .
No .
But close .
More like vinegar .
Like vinegar in the soup .
Yeah . Yeah .
[ Maren sniffing ]
[ breathing laboriously ]
- She 's alive . - [ Sully ] Missy .
- We 'll get help . - Missy .
What did you do to her ?
I found her like that this mornin ' .
You 're lying . Let me by .
Listen . Let me bone down on this .
Whatever you and I got ,
it 's gotta be fed .
[ breathing shakily ]
No . Uh ...
No , ' cause it was ...
It was years before my last time .
[ sighs ] That 's because you 're young .
You 're gonna need it more and more ,
- and more and more . - [ whimpering ]
And you won 't always be able to hold yourself back .
But if the circumstances is ...
is safe and good ,
then eat .
It 'll last a while ,
maybe it 'll keep you from ,
you know , doing something you 'll regret .
[ Maren continues whimpering ]
Even more .
Even more , missy .
Yes , Sully found her that way .
I followed my nose .
I don 't ... I don 't kill people .
At least I try not to .
That leaves this .
- And things like it . - [ sniffles ]
[ sniffles ]
Can I have a few minutes , please ?
Sure , you can .
I don 't think it 'll be a long time now .
When the time comes , you 'll smell it .
[ woman breathing laboriously ]
[ woman gagging ]
[ stops breathing ]
[ sniffling ]
- [ soft footsteps ] - [ Sully breathing heavily ]
[ Sully clears throat ]
- [ body being dragged ] - [ Sully grunting ]
[ body thuds ]
- [ sniffs ] - [ Sully coughing ]
[ crunching and slurping ]
[ Maren breathes excitedly ]
[ both slurping and munching ]
[ yawning ]
[ groans ]
[ sniffs ]
This is how I do it .
It helps me to remember each one .
When I began this , I was about your age .
Pull it .
You won 't break it .
[ chuckles ]
It 's strong . [ laughs ]
[ Maren ] Who was your first ? You remember ?
I ate my own granddad
while they were waiting on the undertaker .
Did anyone find you while you were doing it ?
My mama .
My mama found me afterwards .
Cleaned me up .
She told everyone animals got in and did it .
But when I finally ran off ,
no one came looking for me .
[ Maren ] And you 've been on your own since then ?
It 's not hard ...
once someone teaches you .
[ sniffs ]
But you don 't ... you don 't , uh ...
you don 't need to be alone .
You can bond with me as long as you like .
I 'm looking for someone .
Your mama .
You mentioned your daddy last night ,
so I knew he was in the picture .
You must be runnin ' from him
or he left you or somethin ' .
[ flies buzzing ]
But you didn 't say nothin ' about your mama , though .
I never met her .
All I have is the name of the town she was born in .
It 's on my birth certificate .
Mm-hmm .
We better clean up
before we dry stuck to these chairs .
- [ flies continue buzzing ] - [ grunts ]
[ Sully singing ] ♪ Beautiful , beautiful brown eyes
♪ Beautiful , beautiful brown
[ flies continue buzzing ]
♪ Beautiful , beautiful brown eyes ♪
[ men chattering ]
[ Maren 's father ] The next few , I didn 't see .
A boy went missin ' at a camp you went to .
I shouldn 't have let you go .
But you wanted to .
It was just a week . You were eight .
When that boy went missin ' , I knew
this is who you are .
I never thought " what " you are .
I don 't know if I loved you the way a father should ,
but I ... I didn 't hate you .
You ...
You ate them . I believed you had to .
I don 't know why .
They found his pup tent pitched in the heavy woods ,
all bloody inside .
Luke somethin ' Vanderbilt .
[ driver on PA ] Good evening , everyone .
[ Maren 's father ] They ruled it a homicide ,
I ... I never heard .
[ driver ] This is the end of the line .
[ Maren 's father ] Vanderwall or somethin ' like that .
[ driver ] Take all your belongings with you .
[ Maren 's father ] I watched after to see
if you looked sad , and you didn 't .
That was the beginnin ' of sayin ' no to things .
Now you know why for that , too .
[ music playing on speakers ]
[ man ] So I was thinking ...
[ indistinct chatter ]
[ woman ] No . It 's not there .
You don 't have Lunchables ?
What kind of goddamned grocery store
runs out of Lunchables ?
[ woman 2 ] Excuse me .
Whoa , you trying to run me down ?
I asked a question .
Hear this , you dumb ho .
Hey , don 't talk to her like that !
Hey !
You 're out of control , buddy .
You with the store or somethin ' ?
No , I 'm not with the store ,
but I 'm gonna escort you out of it .
[ chuckles ] Fucking see what happens .
- See what happens ? - Yeah .
What 's gonna happen ? Something bad 's gonna happen ?
Yeah .
[ laughs ] Outside . We 're going outside .
[ boy ] You enjoy hassling people , man ?
Is that what you do on Saturdays
when you 're done jerking off ?
[ man 2 ] Hey , gimme my hat , you little jackass .
- [ breathing heavily ] - [ pensive music playing ]
[ sniffling ]
[ squelching ]
He 's over in there , like , 400 yards if you wanna ...
[ Maren ] You could tell , in the store ?
I smelled you too . I didn 't know I could do that .
I 'm , uh , going to Minnesota .
I got dumped here by a ride . I just stole dinner .
It was all I could think to do .
You 're not local either , I guess .
Why does that matter ?
That was nice what you did for that mom in there .
I 'm 18 , if you 're wondering .
I was gonna guess younger .
Thanks .
I don 't usually talk to anyone after .
I don 't actually meet many others .
Sort of glad not to .
[ Maren ] Yeah , I get it .
[ boy ] I 'm just saying I 'm not an asshole .
You should probably go anyway . Up close , you can see blood .
We 're fine .
No .
I really don 't think I am .
You wanna get in for a minute ?
This truck 's his . You can 't just take it .
Everyone 's got their rules .
That 's not one of my rules .
" Barry Cook .
" 5278 Route 13 . Centerville , Indiana . "
You 're going to his house ?
Yeah , he didn 't have any pictures in his wallet . I think it 'll be all right .
- Took his wallet , too ? - I didn 't take his wallet ,
I took the money out of the wallet . Eight bucks .
I chucked the wallet in a creek back there .
I 'm Maren .
I 'm Lee .
I don 't know whether to cry , or scream , or laugh , or what .
Don 't scream .
I thought I was the only one .
Now I meet two others in a week .
Hey , do you think you could help me ?
- [ sighs ] - I 'm new at this .
No one our age is new at this .
Well , I 'm new at remembering it .
At all .
Look , I won 't try to mess with you . I promise .
I don 't wanna hurt anybody .
- [ Lee ] Famous last words . - [ engine starts ]
[ knocking on door ]
[ door opens ]
[ door closes ]
He 's got Lick It Upby Kiss .
That 's the one where they stop wearing make-up .
Who ?
[ Lee ] You don 't know Lick It Up ?
You don 't know Kiss ?
You were home-schooled , I guess .
Smells like he 'd been getting stoned in here for 30 years .
Wait , this is it . He has it ! Lick It Up .
[ " Lick It Up " by Kiss plays loudly ]
Fuck .
♪ Yeah , yeah ♪
You know ?
[ sings along ] ♪ Don 't wanna wait till you know me better ♪
♪ Let 's just be glad for the time together ♪
♪ Life 's such a treat And it 's time you taste it ♪
♪ There ain 't a reason on earth to waste it ♪
♪ It ain 't a crime to be good to yourself ♪
♪ Lick it up ♪
♪ Oh , oh-oh ! ♪
♪ It 's only right now Lick it up ♪
♪ Lick it up ♪
I 'mma take a shower .
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Lick it up ♪
♪ Oh , oh-oh ! ♪
♪ Come on , c ome on ♪
♪ Lick it up ♪
♪ Oh , oh-oh ! ♪
[ shower running ]
♪ Don 't need to wait for an invitation ♪
[ indistinct tv chatter ]
[ commentator 1 on TV ] Here comes Robert Ford there ,
interfering where he 's got no place .
- Disqualification on Eric . - [ commentator 2 ] Yeah .
Boyd jumps up in the ring . Robs Jarrett .
Keith Eric starts to kick on him ,
and Fuller says no , bam , and he throws ...
[ eerie music playing ]
[ Maren moaning softly ]
[ Maren 's father ] It 's your birthday .
I 've been waiting on this day for a long time .
- [ blows ] - [ Maren gasps ]
[ indistinct TV chatter ]
You seemed like such a hardcase yesterday .
When you weigh 140 pounds wet ,
you gotta have a big attitude instead .
I 've got that for you .
- And the pancakes . - Thanks .
- And your bacon . - Thank you .
Sully .
That 's his name . The other guy I met .
He showed up at a bus station
saying he could smell me half a mile away .
- Can you do that ? - Not that far .
Said he could also smell
when people are about to die too .
Actually , I think I might have heard of this guy .
- Really ? - Yeah .
Keeps this braid woven with the hair .
People that he eats .
- Christ . - It 's like eight feet long .
[ Lee ] That 's a choice .
We don 't have to be like that .
Why didn 't you tag along with him ?
[ Maren ] Mm ...
Something about him . I don 't know .
I think he was tryin ' to help .
I profoundly doubt that .
He was creepy , I guess .
Did that dawn on you before or after
[ softly ] you ate Mrs. Herman together ?
[ waitress ] More coffee ?
- [ clears throat ] Yes , please . - Okay .
Can I get anything else for you guys ?
That 's all right . That 's good , thanks .
You 're welcome .
- Harmon . Mrs. Harmon . - Mrs ... Mrs. Harmon .
[ waitress ] Okay . You 're welcome .
Does that help ?
Memorizing their names ?
[ sighs ]
Why 'd you offer to bring me along ?
You seem nice .
- I am nice . - Mm .
Do I seem nice ?
I 'm going to the bathroom .
How do you feel about sleeping outside ?
Okay .
[ growls playfully ]
[ Lee ] It 'll be cold tonight , but if we keep this truck ,
we 'll get a sheet of plywood for back here .
[ Maren ] What 's in Kentucky anyway ?
[ Lee ] It 's my little sister .
I promised to give her driving lessons
before she has to take her test .
[ Maren ] Mm . [ Lee ] She 's a good kid .
[ Maren ] Do you get home often ?
[ Lee ] A little bit . I left when I was 17 .
- [ thunder cracking ] - [ Maren ] How come ?
[ Lee ] I didn 't finish school , which sucks .
I 'm guessing you didn 't , either .
Other ways to learn , I guess .
[ preacher on radio ] Maybe what other peoples '
weaknesses may be .
That Satan knows where your weakness is .
I said He knows where your weakness is .
He knows how to stir you up .
I said He knows how to stir you up .
And He knows [ chuckles ]
that one of my weaknesses that I will confess to
is the ability to hate you to the bitter end .
We 'll stay here tonight . This is my aunt 's place .
She died in March .
My house 's on the other side of that plant .
I can 't be seen in town , though .
You need to know why ?
No .
What 's gonna happen to all this stuff ?
[ Lee ] My mom 's cleanin ' it out .
She 's a teacher , though . She got school .
No , keep that off .
And keep the windows closed tonight too .
Okay , I 'mma take Kayla drivin ' behind the mall .
Hope I don 't die .
I 'll bring back some food for us later .
Kayla 's your sister ?
Yeah . Kay ,
Kayla . I call her " idiot " to her face .
Or " stupid . " Or whatever .
You can snoop around if you want , I won 't be offended .
See you later .
Lock the door .
[ door closes ]
[ locks door ]
[ both laughing ]
- [ banging on door ] - [ girl ] Lee , open up
the goddam door , asshole .
I know you 're in there .
Man , open up this door , Lee . Let 's go .
[ Lee ] Why are you banging on the fucking door ?
What the fuck are you doing here ?
Nice work , you motard .
Found this note you put in my purse .
You 're leaving ? Already ?
Maren , this is Kayla . Kayla , this is Maren .
You 're a fuckin ' asshole .
You said that you were gonna stick around this time .
Something came up . I gotta head out of town .
I ... I don 't believe you anymore , Lee .
I ... Where are you always going anyway ?
[ Lee ] Let 's go outside , come on .
I wanna talk to you outside .
I 'm going away for a little bit , all right ? That 's it .
[ Kayla ] Is that your girlfriend ?
[ Lee ] That 's my friend friend , all right ?
Maybe you can meet her some other time .
Look , I can 't stay , Kayla .
I just wanted to take you drivin ' like I said I would .
[ Kayla ] I fuckin ' hate that you do this .
You know , Dad did this , and then he didn 't come back .
Don 't you know every time you drive off , we 're terrified ?
[ Lee ] I 'll be back in a couple of weeks .
What difference does it make ?
[ Kayla ] You 're not listenin ' to me .
[ Lee ] Yes , I am . Two weeks tops .
I 'm not Dad . I wouldn 't do that .
[ Kayla ] Is there anything that you don 't lie about ?
And you look like a fucking faggot in that shirt .
Honestly , fuck you , Lee . Fuck you .
[ door opens , slams ]
[ lee breathing shakily ]
[ softly ] God , fuck it , man .
[ exhales heavily ]
Let 's go tonight .
She 's probably gonna tell my mom that we 're here .
If she comes , I ...
I wanna spare you that . [ chuckles ]
[ sighs ]
I worked summers here . I can 't get in the safe ,
but they keep all the petty cash in a drawer in the cafe .
[ Maren ] A cafe ? At a slaughterhouse ?
Aren 't there guards ?
[ Lee ] Yeah . Dale .
Deaf in both ears .
You be the bank . [ panting ]
I wanna show you something .
[ cows mooing ]
[ Lee ] The music 's supposed to keep ' em calm .
You ever think about that ...
every one of them has a mom and a dad ...
sisters , brothers , cousins , kids .
Friends even ?
[ cow moos ]
A language .
Listen to them .
[ cows continue mooing ]
You never told me what was in Minnesota .
My mom .
She lives there ?
I don 't know .
I don 't even know if she 's still alive .
All I have is the name of the town that she was born in .
Could take a while to track her down , you know .
It might even be a dead end .
It 's all I have .
Then that 's where we 'll start .
I can take you ...
if you want . It 's a lot of driving ,
but I 'm up for it , if you are .
We could take our time . See the country .
Well , Missouri and Iowa anyway .
- Never been to either . - [ chuckles softly ]
[ indistinct chatter on radio ]
[ on radio ] ♪ Amarillo by mornin ' ♪
[ singing along ] ♪ Up from San Antone ♪
♪ Everything that I got ♪
♪ Is just what I 've got on ♪
Whoo-hoo !
[ Maren ] What was your first time like ?
[ smacks lips ] It was a babysitter .
- Mine too . - Really ?
What was it like ?
A rush .
I could feel every blood vessel
like spider-webbing through me .
Felt like some kind of weird new superhero .
[ chuckles softly ]
What about afterward ?
What 'd you feel about it ? What 'd you think ?
- I don 't remember after . - [ scoffs ]
That 's bullshit .
Hey , I 'm not just gonna tell you what you wanna hear .
You asked me a question , I gotta answer it .
Would you do something with me ?
- Listen to something with me ? - Yeah .
[ vehicle approaching ]
Whoo ! I told you they 'd be back here .
[ both laugh ]
- Hey . - Hey .
I saw you guys down at the swimming hole before .
Oh , yeah , we saw some people down there too .
You were up there on those rocks .
Up , uh ...
Upwind of us .
You get me ?
Don 't worry , we 're friendly .
I 'm Jake . That 's , uh , Bradley .
Goddamn , my name is Brad , man . Call me what I want .
Nice to meet you , Brad . Nice to meet you , Jake .
I 'm Leon . That 's Maggie .
You just passing through ?
Yeah , just passing through . Is that a problem ?
We 're not here to run you out .
We thought you might be in need of some beer .
We got you .
[ Jake ] Not many come through here .
- What do you say ? - [ sighs softly ]
I 'm into this now , right ?
Pulling meat , bones comin ' out , you know .
[ can pops open ]
And I start feeling watched .
I look around and at first , I don 't see him ' cause he 's ...
he 's standing so still in the trees ,
but then I spot him . I 'm like , " What the fuck ? "
I mean , I look like the red devil at this point .
He 's just watching me like I 'm ...
[ Brad laughs ]
Doug fuckin ' Henning .
[ gasping spookily ]
[ jake and brad laughing ]
I 'm already on my feet , and I 'm runnin ' at him ,
and he pulls a fuckin ' pistol on me .
Turns out he 's an off-duty cop .
- First year on the force . - We did
say we weren 't gonna tell nobody about that .
Oh , right , right .
So , he 's a cop .
[ Brad chuckles ]
I think he 's gonna take me down . But he 's just ...
he 's just looking at me .
And what did I say ?
He said , " Do me now or get the fuck gone
" ' cause he ain 't gonna be no fun to eat cold . "
- [ both laughing ] - I love it .
[ cackling ]
So he says ...
" Go on , back to it . Mm-hmm .
" I gotta get a better look at this . "
[ smacks lips ]
[ chuckles ] So , uh ...
I suddenly feel him right there ,
crouched down , gettin ' a better look .
He doesn 't smell like an Eater .
But there he is .
So I ask if he wants some .
And damned if he don 't nod all serious
like a food-stamp kid on samples day .
- Yeah . - [ Jake ] So you know
what I gave him ?
You 're not one of us ?
Abso-fucking-lutely normal he is ! [ laughs ]
- Well , uh , clearly not normal . - [ laughs ]
Hasn 't had his Full Bones yet . But , uh ...
I reckon that 's coming soon enough .
" Full Bones " ?
When you eat the whole thing . Bones and all .
You ain 't done that yet ?
That 's a big fucking deal .
It 's like your first time .
There 's ...
before Bones and all ,
and then there 's after .
That 's bullshit .
It 's impossible , what you 're talking about .
How many people have you eaten ?
[ Jake ] I count three .
Yes , miss .
Three people .
And you didn 't have to ?
You don 't have to do this ?
Kind of a groupie , I guess .
- Jesus Christ . - You okay ?
Jake 's teaching me how to smell other Eaters .
No , he 's not .
You don 't think he can do it ?
[ Brad ] Is she all right ?
[ indistinct conversation ]
[ Brad ] Whoa . Fuck . Fuck .
She 's lucky she 's got you to help .
[ urinating ]
God .
He 's the one who needs the help , Brad .
[ chuckles ]
You can see it a mile away .
You remind me of every junkie I ever met .
You look like the kind that 's convinced himself
he 's got this under his thumb .
But you pull on one little thread and ...
[ mimics swishing ]
But maybe love will set you free , man .
[ Jake chuckles ]
Maybe love will set you
free .
[ guffawing ]
[ unsettling music playing ]
[ snoring ]
[ door shuts gently ]
Lee , Lee .
What ?
- What ? - Look . Look , look , look .
[ groans ]
[ unsettling music intensifying ]
Go , go , go , go , go , go .
[ yells ]
[ laughs ]
[ ride passengers screaming ]
[ vendor ] Hot dogs !
[ man ] Roll up . Roll up .
[ lively chatter ]
I 'm hungry , Lee .
We should do that right over there .
Yeah , we have four tickets .
- Okay . - Yes .
[ man 1 ] Step right up . We 've got big prizes .
[ man 2 ] Three tickets , three tries .
Three tickets , three tries .
Who wants to play ?
[ man 2 ] Three tickets , three tries .
[ boy ] Can I play ?
You 're wasting your money .
[ rock song playing on speakers ]
Come on .
- [ clang ] - Ah .
I won . I won .
No , you didn 't , little man .
[ boy ] But ... But it 's in a can .
What does that mean ?
What you just did . No underhand .
But that other kid did it .
You can read , can 't you ?
Now go on . Unless you got three more tickets .
Hey , man .
You tryin ' to win one for your girlfriend ? I saw you walk up .
Oh , no , that 's not my girlfriend .
That 's just , uh , a friend , you know . [ chuckles ]
- [ CLANG ] - Nice .
- Wow . - Can I get another one if I sink it again ?
You 're not supposed to .
But , uh , no one has to know .
Damn .
Disappoint .
Hmm .
What 's there to do around here besides this dumbass carnival ?
After my friend leaves , I mean .
I close up at 11 : 00 .
I got some weed in my car .
Hell , yeah .
- One more ? - Really ?
Yeah .
- Damn . [ laughs ] - Damn .
Lucky , lucky .
My luck 's not gonna run out , is it ?
No , man .
I 'll see that it don 't .
I 'll see you in an hour ?
Yeah , you will .
[ Maren 's father on tape ] I haven 't thought much beyond this tape .
I can 't .
I don 't know what 's going to happen to you
or what should happen to you .
I wake up nights sick to death wondering and hoping .
Hoping that whatever troubles you is over ,
and that if there is a God in Heaven ,
that you 're just a regular girl
with ... regular problems and regular pain ,
and that you stop wanting things
you shouldn 't want , Maren .
And that your heart has a chance .
[ tape button clicks ]
I knew that 's how it would end .
" I hope you get better . "
Maybe he 's right , maybe I should pray
that I wake up one day
to find they built a maze around me .
Don 't say that .
Don 't .
He 's wrong .
[ Lee sighs ]
What happened to your dad ?
You never say anything .
Nothing good .
Just a waste .
- [ door shuts in distance ] - [ soft footsteps ]
Except in my case , I gave him the tape .
[ footsteps approaching ]
Just give me a couple of minutes .
You made it .
- [ Lee ] This is a good spot . - Yeah , it 's not bad .
[ Lee ] There 's no one here .
- [ man ] Is that you ? - [ Lee ] Yeah .
- [ man ] It 's a nice truck . - [ Lee ] Great , huh ?
[ man ] Yeah , she is . I 'm parked up there .
Do you smoke ?
What are you laughing about ?
- Do you smoke weed too ? - [ Lee ] Yeah .
[ man chuckles ] You kinky fucker .
[ both laughing ]
[ rustling ]
[ man moaning ]
[ man ] Oh , yeah .
Faster , man . Jerk it faster . Come on .
I 'm close , yeah . Yeah , like that .
[ man breathing rapidly ]
Come on , come on , faster , man .
Faster , faster . [ inhales sharply ]
Oh , yeah .
[ unnerving music playing ]
Oh , fuck !
Oh .
[ man breathing rapidly ]
Faster , jerk it faster , man . Come on .
Yeah , I 'm close . I 'm close .
Just like that .
I 'm close , I 'm close . Here it comes . Here it comes .
That sure feels ... [ gasps ]
- [ body thuds ] - [ Lee breathing heavily ]
[ man choking and gurgling ]
- [ Lee panting ] - [ gagging ]
[ munching ]
[ radio host ] The world in the spring
and a new skateboard from Bikes Unlimited .
[ tuning radio ]
[ radio host 2 ] Don 't you love the smell of black rubber ?
Maybe not .
It 's an acquired taste .
Some people never get used to it .
Don 't really understand .
Oh , you can work your way up .
[ radio chatter continues indistinctly ]
What 's wrong ?
[ Lee ] That 's the place listed on his license ,
but the lights are on .
I 'm gonna go back and see if anyone 's there .
No , no , I 'll go , I 'll go . You have blood on you .
I cleaned up . He had wipes in the car .
You can take them if you want .
I 'll see what I can see from the yard .
Okay .
[ radio host 2 ] All black . Completely hidden .
In my black cocoon , I 'm where no one can find me .
[ Maren panting ]
Maren , you okay ?
What are you doing ?
What ? Oh , Christ .
Okay , we didn 't know .
Hey , we didn 't know , okay ? [ tuts ]
[ woman 1 ] Is he back ?
[ woman 2 ] No ! Something 's wrong , Mom !
All right , we gotta go . Let 's go , let 's go , let 's go .
Focus , focus . Come on , let 's go .
[ radio host ] Only there did civilization arise .
Now , it 's not my intention to give a history lesson ,
but I believe it 's important to remind ourselves
that in dealing with the economy ,
we 're dealing with human creativity .
This insight has represented
the underpinning of our economic expansion .
There wasn 't a car seat , Maren .
He wasn 't wearing a wedding ring .
We should feel something .
' Cause we murder people .
We steal their stuff , we move the fuck on ,
and we ruin lives that we don 't even see .
Come on , why are we talking about it like this ?
We gotta do this ! We have to do it !
[ sniffles ]
[ Maren ] Talking about the future ,
talking about being a friend to yourself .
You don 't have that . This is too much .
No , we got 60 , 70 years of this ?
How dare you make this harder .
Maren , what do I ... What am I supposed ...
How do I get you out of this ?
What am I supposed to say right now ?
Just drive .
Right . All right .
[ Maren breathing heavily ]
[ gasping ]
[ Lee ] You were dreaming . We 're almost there .
[ chuckles ]
[ patrons chattering ]
Uh , do have a telephone book ? The one outside 's missing .
Uh ...
I 'm looking for someone in Bagley .
Oh . This is for the county , sweetie .
[ breathing heavily ]
[ Maren ] Thanks .
There .
- I 'll come with you . - No , stay here .
Excuse me ? Are you Barbara Kerns ?
Wait , wait . Ms. Kerns . Ms. Kerns .
I 'm Maren Yearly .
Maren .
I 've traveled a very long way .
Oh , they didn 't marry .
Hmm . Yeah , we wondered .
Huh .
My husband , uh , he died years ago .
Throat cancer .
- Sorry . - Mm .
Sorry to surprise you like this .
You didn 't know your daughter had a child , I guess .
No .
No . When she wanted to get married ,
we didn 't agree .
So , it drove her away . Yeah .
Where did she meet my dad ?
He didn 't say ?
He wouldn 't say anything about her .
Ah .
Hmm . Mm .
[ sighs ]
They met in college . Down in Mankato .
She finished two years
before he talked her into leaving .
Did he drive you here ? Is he outside ?
No . He 's in Maryland .
Does he know you 're here ?
Yeah , he let me know where to find you .
So you haven 't run away ?
No .
My dad thinks that
I 'm old enough to live on my own .
Oh . Uh-huh .
Well , if you 're looking for a home with your mother ,
um ,
I 'm sorry to tell you
that she ... she 's no longer with us .
What ? When ?
It 's a lot of years now ,
and it 's nothing I wanna tell you about .
I hope you can respect that .
Well , I 'm her daughter .
Yep . Makes sense now .
Why she came back so bereaved . That 's the word .
And she wouldn 't tell us anything , either .
Oh , it 's just so much hiding in one family .
I 'm sorry you had to be the child of it all .
Wait . What was she like as a child ?
Hmm .
Wow . She was your only child ?
[ Barbara ] Well , not even ours .
Bob and I never could have babies of our own .
But then we heard about Janelle .
She 'd been left behind
a sheriff 's station in Bemidji .
It was in the paper .
You know anything about her biological parents ?
No , nothing .
Except what they did to their baby .
I mean , she could have froze , you know .
It 's cold here all the time .
My mother ...
You can , you know , take those photos if you want ' em .
Did she ever hurt anyone ?
What kind of question is that ?
I bet she did . I know she did .
I don 't know what you had to do to cover it up
or ... how much pain it caused you .
Stop this . At once .
Look , you 're never going to see me again , okay ?
You may not be her family by blood , but I am .
And I need to know .
So , please , Mrs. Kerns , please ...
Then ask her yourself .
How ?
[ sighs ]
Look , I don 't know you .
You gotta understand .
I didn 't know what you wanted comin ' up here .
And I hope you mean what you say
about never coming back here .
I know that sounds cold , but I wanna be clear with ya .
I told you she was no longer with us ,
but she 's not ... she 's not dead .
She 's living in a town called Fergus Falls .
In a state hospital there .
And we didn 't put her there ,
if that 's what you 're thinkin ' .
She signed her own papers .
[ door opens ]
[ door closes ]
[ panting ] Okay .
Here . My mother 's here .
Do you want me to come in ?
No .
[ nurse ] Mrs. Kerns ' daughter .
I sure didn 't expect this when I woke up this morning .
[ muffled shouting ]
[ woman screaming ]
[ woman 2 ] Calm down .
Calm down .
Is she dangerous ?
It 's been many years since that was a concern .
[ woman 3 crying ]
Why was it ever one ?
Aggression towards the staff . Self-harm .
But long ago .
[ keys jingling ]
It 's possible she won 't understand who you are .
She just took her morning meds ,
so she may nod off anyhow .
We 'll see .
There 's someone here to see you , Ms. Kerns .
A surprise . A wonderful surprise .
[ Maren ] It 's Maren .
I 'm Maren .
Can 't she speak ?
It 's the medication .
[ whimpers , breathing shakily ]
Easy , Ms. Kerns .
I didn 't come with Dad .
I didn 't come with Dad . Just came by myself .
Should I give her the letter , Ms. Kerns ?
I fetched it on the way up .
[ whimpering ]
She wrote this about 15 years ago now , must be .
I 've kept it safe in her file out there , in case .
She knew I 'd come ?
I 'll wait right over here .
[ Janelle ] Maren , if a day comes when you show up here ,
I 'll know it 's because your father broke his promise .
Told you something about me .
And I 'll know why .
He didn 't know what I was when we married ,
but he figured it out by the time I had you .
I promised I would never hurt either of you ,
but how could we be sure ?
It wasn 't easy to leave . I loved you both so much .
I thought about ending my life ,
but I wanted to be here in case you ever did come .
All I ever wanted in this world was love .
I tried , believed ,
but we can 't have it as we are .
All we can have is a little space ,
with bars or a door that locks .
[ tearfully ] I 'm sorry for that , Little Yearly .
For all the things I didn 't do for you
and for the one thing I still can .
The world of love
- wants no monsters in it . - [ breathing heavily ]
So let me help you out of it .
- [ growling ] - [ Maren gasping ]
[ Maren ] No ! Help me !
Ms. Kerns , calm down !
Maren , die .
[ Maren ] Let me out . Let me out .
Press the button on the door . Go !
[ gasping ]
[ blubbering ]
[ door rattling ]
I can 't open the door . I can 't open the door .
[ Lee ] Sorry , sorry . Here we go , here we go .
[ Maren ] I can 't fucking with the door .
[ Lee ] You 're good .
[ Maren ] She 's one of us .
She 's one of us but she 's fucking nuts .
She ate her own fucking hands .
She said she loved my dad .
She said she wanted to be a mom .
She could have stayed .
She could have told me what I needed to know .
But all of this ... Fuck , you know how different
this would 've been if I 'd had one person on my side ?
One person to talk to ?
You know what I wouldn 't have done ?
Maybe , probably half of what I 've fucking done !
Fuck her . Fuck .
[ Lee ] You know , if she 'd stayed ,
she might have hurt you , Maren . Or worse , you might not even be here right now .
Trust me , I know what I 'm talking about with this stuff .
This is better than what I went through .
Please just stop fucking talking !
You 're pissed off , and you 're scared , and you feel alone ,
and you don 't know what to do with it all , it 's fine .
If you wanna go at yourself with that , I can 't stop you .
But don 't come at me .
You slit his throat , Lee .
- He had a wife . Kids . - Okay .
I think you got used to being locked up
and invisible and alone , and now you 're out in the world ...
- Okay , okay . - And you 're seeing yourself
for the first time , and that 's freaking you out .
But you know what ? It 's fucking me up too , okay ?
I feel like I 'm seeing myself too . That 's how this works .
- How what works ? - This !
Whatever this is .
Stop . You 're wrong , you 're wrong .
What ? About which part am I wrong ?
I can 't be around you anymore . I can 't think .
Jesus Christ .
We don 't have many options , Maren .
Either you eat , you off yourself ,
or you lock yourself up like her in there .
What 's it gonna be ?
Why can 't you let me have this ?
[ sighs ]
No .
I 'm not going to be her . I 'm not going to be her .
You can decide no .
And I 'm deciding that right fucking now .
I 'm just getting gas .
You have the money .
[ Lee sighs ]
[ Lee ] Maren !
Maren !
[ singing ] ♪ Beautiful , beautiful brown eyes ♪
♪ Beautiful , beautiful brown eyes ♪
[ chuckles ]
♪ I 'll never love blue eyes again ♪
Hey , hey .
You ain 't sad to see old Sully , are you , missy ?
It worked out . [ chuckling ]
I hardly believe it .
You 've been following me since Frederick ?
[ laughs ]
I know . It seems crazy to me too . I ...
I just didn 't ... I didn 't know what else to do .
Why , Sully ?
Well , because we ...
we didn 't have a chance to say our goodbyes .
And I 've been worrying on you on your own as you are .
Why not say hello earlier then ?
Oh , no , no , missy . I don 't ...
I don 't interrupt . That 's bad manners ,
and you were with a friend .
And where 'd he go now ? I saw him .
Took off out of here fast .
Is he your new boyfriend ? Is he ?
[ Maren ] No , no , no .
Or just a hobo you 're hanging around with ?
No , I 'm just a friend .
Oh , just a friend .
Maybe he didn 't get that telegram .
He one of us ?
Follow your nose or he follow his ?
- [ Maren ] Both . - [ laughing ]
Thanks for showing me how .
[ continues laughing ]
Hey , count the bugs .
Well , life 's never dully with Sully .
What do you say ? Uh ...
What do you say ? You wanna , uh ,
take a ride with Sully for a bit ?
It 's weird that you 've been following me .
It 's only been a couple of weeks .
Life will get weirder , I promise . I promise .
I liked ...
I liked our talk .
Oh , it 's a hard and lonesome road for us , isn 't it ?
So , there 's no sense in making it lonelier
[ stammering ] if you don 't have to .
- I 'm a girl . - I know .
About my daughter 's age ,
if I had one . [ chuckles ]
Is that what this is ?
[ sighs ]
How do you like that ?
Sully , I 'm not trying to upset you . Mm-hmm .
Just , I know you drove a long way .
I don 't feel comfortable with this .
You 've never fit with someone before ?
I have .
It 's just gotta go both ways .
[ sighs ]
You don 't like Sully .
Why do you say your name
like you 're two different people ?
You don 't like me .
No , I don 't trust you .
It doesn 't matter if I 'm right or if I 'm wrong about that ,
it just matters that I feel it .
So you 're not gettin ' in ?
Not gettin ' in .
Fuck you , then .
Fuck you , missy .
You dumb cunt !
I ...
I dried off next to you .
I 've never done that with anyone before .
That means something .
I dried off next to ...
[ tires screech ]
[ indistinct chatter ]
[ music playing on speakers ]
[ waitress ] Your coffee .
Thanks .
[ man ] How many times you gonna tell her
before she starts to listen ?
[ waitress ] Hi , guys . [ officer ] Hey , Sheila .
- Good to see you . - [ waitress ] Be right with you .
[ soft grunt ]
[ man ] Stay with Daddy , all right ?
[ kid ] I 'm bouncing so high .
I don 't know . Just come on , Daddy , watch me .
Watch me .
[ man ] There 's glass all over here . Get over here .
[ kid ] Coming , Daddy .
[ footsteps approaching ]
[ disembodied door opens ]
[ door closes ]
[ man panting ]
[ struggling grunts ]
[ scuffling ]
[ metal clacking ]
I love you .
[ muffled shouting ]
[ struggling grunts ]
[ man screaming ]
[ gasps ]
[ breath trembling ]
- [ music playing inside ] - [ line ringing ]
[ Kayla ] Hello ?
[ Lee ] Hey , idiot , how are you doin ' ?
Is it too late to call ?
Where are you ? You sound weird .
I 'm driving home , actually .
Will you be here tonight ?
Yeah , I 'll be there super late ,
but yeah , I 'll get there .
Can you stay ?
This time , I can . Yeah .
- I 'm really glad , Lee . - [ laughs ]
Me too .
Hey , what do you think about hittin ' the kingdom when I 'm back ?
Going for a drive or something , huh ?
Are you crying ?
No . What ?
Are ... Are you in trouble ?
No , I 'm driving home . I 'm good .
- [ exhales heavily ] - Can I tell Mom you 're coming ?
Sure you can .
Sure .
- [ line disconnects ] - [ breathes deeply ]
I don 't even care about chores .
- [ LAUGHTER ] - That 's all I care about .
- It 's so ... - You 're right .
[ Kayla ] I mean , I cared about it before ,
- but not anymore . - [ girl ] Yeah . Exactly .
Hey , Kayla .
I 'm Maren , Lee 's friend .
I met you at your aunt 's house a couple of months back .
I remember .
I 'll talk to y 'all in a minute .
[ Maren ] Yeah , I wanted to say hi then , but ...
Do you know where Lee is ?
He was at my aunt 's house for a while ,
but my mom wouldn 't leave him alone ,
so he took his tent and moved out to the lake .
Which lake ?
Um , Land Between the Lakes .
It 's a state park down 641 .
He comes into town when he wants to .
Well , he 's just ...
going through something , I guess .
But I asked him about you
and he just said that you went another way .
I wondered why he 's been staying .
I guess he was hoping that you 'd show up , right ?
No , I don 't know about that .
I don 't know if he 'd actually even want to see me ,
to be honest .
I know he was trying to get back to you , though .
He said that ?
[ chuckles ] God , he 's an asshole .
Why is he even like this , you know ?
I tell him no one even remembers
all that stuff with the cops anymore .
It was three stupid days and they let him go .
This is about your dad ?
He didn 't tell you ?
Our dad 's a drunk .
So drunk that he 'd piss on the wall kinda guy .
He got in Lee 's face a couple of times
and Lee would , you know , try to calm him down ,
and the day he left , he wound up hitting Lee .
And when I tried to break ' em up , he hit me , too .
Lee just lost it ,
and he told me to call the cops .
And when our dad ripped the phone out of the wall ,
Lee got him in a headlock . He told me to run into town .
And when I got back with the cops ,
Lee was pretty beat up and Dad 's car was gone .
And Lee told ' em that he took off ,
but there was blood on Lee ,
so they had to put him in a holding cell
so they could test it .
And for a minute there , everyone was like ,
" Lee killed him , Lee killed him . "
But it was all Lee 's blood .
It was all bullshit , and they had to let him go .
And that was four years ago ,
and he 's been out of town for three and a half of ' em .
It 's not fair .
[ children chattering ]
[ Maren ] Lee !
- [ fireworks exploding ] - [ dog barking ]
- [ people exclaiming ] - [ Maren ] Your tent .
We should really use it . Just get lost .
[ Lee ] Where do you want to go ?
I don 't know . Anywhere . West . Let 's go west .
[ laughs ]
[ mechanic ] It 's your rod bearings then .
[ Lee ] Seriously ? Shit !
That means a new engine .
I 'd rather just sell it for parts .
Tell you what , you make me a good offer , I 'll sell it to you right now .
[ splutters ] You don 't want to sell it out here .
- [ Lee ] Why ? - Look around , man .
How you gonna get home ?
I don 't know .
You do go someplace else .
[ Maren ] Watching me read ?
[ Lee ] Yeah .
[ Maren ] Well , you should know after this , I 'm out of books .
I 'll have to go to a bookstore .
[ Lee ] May have to stop on the way back , in Omaha .
By the way , those guys were saying
we should have two days of water with us
in case the engine gives out .
In case we have to wait on a ride .
We should get some new wheels as soon as we can .
I wish we could save it .
I 'd rather have a van , anyway .
I learned how to drive in that truck .
You learned how to kiss in that truck .
I knew how to kiss before you , Mr. Kentucky .
Ah .
I sang to my girl in that truck .
Kayla told me about ...
what happened with your dad .
Kayla doesn 't know what happened .
He sounds like he was a fucking asshole .
[ Lee ] I don 't wanna ...
I don 't want to talk about my dad .
I don 't sweat this stuff out like you do .
You know , Kayla said that he ...
that he hit you both the day that he left .
That 's true .
Told her to get the cops . She did .
And then he left .
I don 't know , I don 't really believe that . I mean ,
there must 've been a lot of blood on you for the cops to bring you in .
If you wanna know , Maren , he came for me , okay ?
He tried to rip me open with his teeth .
That 's the first time I ever smelled it on someone .
What happened after that ?
[ Lee sighs ]
Lee ,
you can tell me .
[ Lee sighs , tuts ]
[ exhales heavily ] He , uh ...
He passed out .
I got him in a ... I put him in a fucking ... [ sniffles ]
headlock , and bashed an ashtray over his head .
Dragged his fucking body to his car .
Put him in the car ,
and I drove to this barn about a mile outside town
that I knew was abandoned .
[ sniffles ]
How long was he in the barn ?
Uh , three days .
I think , yeah .
Three days .
I duct-taped the shit out of him too .
Everywhere except his nostrils ,
so he could breathe .
And when I finally came back ...
It 's the sound he was making ,
it 's the noise and the breathing .
He knew what was gonna happen .
[ exhales heavily ]
[ Maren sniffles ]
What did you do ?
I ate him right the fuck up .
And it felt fucking great .
I felt high as a motherfucker . [ inhales sharply ]
Probably would have killed myself
if it weren 't for Kayla .
I feel like I should have , you know .
No . No , stop .
[ Lee breathes heavily ]
I would have done the same thing .
- Do you mean it ? - I would have done it in my way but I would have done it .
You protected the people that you love .
You don 't think I 'm a bad person ?
All I think is that I love you .
[ Lee breathes shakily ]
[ Lee exhales deeply ]
[ Lee sniffles ]
[ Lee crying ]
[ Maren ] Where do we go next ?
[ Lee ] Anywhere .
[ Maren ] Let 's drive back .
Until the truck gives out somewhere .
And then just stay .
We can get a place , jobs .
You know , like people do .
[ Lee ] You wanna be people ? Let 's be people .
[ Maren ] Yeah . Let 's be them for a while .
[ Lee ] Yeah , we 're in Ann Arbor now .
Ann Arbor .
Maren got a job at the university ,
at the bookstore , so , we 're right near campus .
What 'd you say ?
Yeah , maybe if we 're here long enough .
Hey , Kayla says hi .
- Hi . - Maren says hi .
- She wants to come up . - Yeah .
[ indistinct chatter ]
Lee , I brought your ...
[ sighs ]
[ breathes deeply ]
- [ Maren whimpering ] - [ shushing ]
[ Sully breathing heavily ]
I 'm gonna take my hand away ,
and you 're not gonna scream .
Because Sully 's a friend
and we don 't scream at friends .
[ gasping ]
Where 's your ... Where 's your cutie-pie ?
[ laughing ]
I saw him .
I saw him walk out of here half an hour ago .
I don 't know .
What 's all this for , Sully ?
Ever ...
Ever since I drove away from you ,
up there in Minnesota ,
nothing 's felt right .
[ Maren ] What does that mean ?
[ smacks lips ]
It means ...
[ breathes heavily ]
It mean ... It ...
It means unfinished business .
Sully , me and Lee ...
we are together now .
[ Maren gasps ]
That 's not the business I 'm talkin ' about .
I don 't mind .
I don 't ... I don 't mind if you don 't like Sully .
What I mind is how much you know about him
in that little head of yours .
You don 't think I 'd tell anyone , right ?
[ Sully groans ]
I mean , who would believe me ?
And you 're the one who told me you don 't kill any ...
You don 't kill , right ?
You told me that , Sully .
You know , I told ...
I used to try and tell people the truth , you know .
They never took me serious .
[ Sully sighs ]
I just wanted to be ...
I just wanted to be with someone who understood .
Do you know what I mean ?
Do you ?
Mm .
[ sniffling ]
Hmm .
[ Sully grunts softly ]
[ door opens quietly ]
[ Maren ] Hey .
You never get sick of yourself ?
Sully just wants to sleep at night .
That 's all .
Sully just wants to sleep .
Sleep it off .
I said ,
stop calling yourself Sully .
Shh !
[ breathing heavily ]
[ screaming ]
[ Lee grunting ]
[ Sully yells ]
[ ALL GRUNTING ]
[ SULLY YELLING ]
[ GROANS ]
Get off , Maren . Get off .
- [ Maren grunting ] - [ Sully groaning ]
[ Sully gasps deeply ]
[ Maren gasping ]
[ Lee grunting ]
[ Lee ] Careful .
Come on .
[ panting and grunting ]
[ sully groaning weakly ]
Up .
[ Sully groaning ]
[ Sully wheezing ]
[ panting ]
[ screaming in pain ]
[ gasping in pain ]
[ gasping deeply ]
[ Sully stops breathing ]
[ panting ]
[ continues panting ]
[ grunting ]
[ Lee ] That 's the man you met , the one who followed you ?
I smelled him two blocks from here .
How the fuck did he find you ?
[ Maren ] Oh , no .
[ Lee coughing ]
[ Lee gasping ]
[ Maren ] Hang on .
[ breathing nervously ]
Look . [ whimpers ]
Fuck , he hit your lung .
We gotta go to the ER .
Air is coming out of this . I can see it .
He got Kayla .
Don 't think about that right now .
[ Lee ] Fuck .
[ Maren ] Lee , we can 't handle this by ourselves , and ...
- Am I bad ? - No .
No , no , Lee . You 're good , all right ?
You 're in shock .
- Am I bad ? - No .
No .
We can 't call an ambulance , Lee .
We can 't let anybody in here .
We 're just gonna go .
Come on .
- I want you to eat first . - Come on , Lee .
- I want you to eat me . - No .
- I want you to eat ... - I 'm not gonna eat him .
- No . I want you to eat ... - I don 't wanna .
I want you to eat me .
I want you to eat .
- I want you to feed . - No .
- I want you to eat . - No .
- I don 't wanna . I can 't . Stop . - I want you to do it , Maren .
[ Lee ] I 'm done here . [ Maren ] No . No . No .
- I want you to do it , Maren . - Lee , stop .
- No . No , I can 't . - Bones and all .
- [ Maren ] I can 't . Stop . - [ Lee coughs ]
[ Lee ] It 's beautiful . [ Maren ] No . No . Stop .
Let me up . Let me up . Let me up .
[ Lee ] It 's the easiest thing , Maren , love .
[ Maren ] No . No . No .
[ Lee ] Just love me and eat .
[ imperceptible ]